[
{"question": "🇧🇴", "response": "Bolivia" }, 
{"question": "🇵🇪", "response": "Peru" }, 
{"question": "🇦🇷", "response": "Argentina" }, 
{"question": "🇧🇫", "response": "Burkina Faso" }, 
{"question": "🇦🇲", "response": "Armenia" }, 
{"question": "🇦🇨", "response": "Canadá" }, 
{"question": "🇦🇪", "response": "Emiratos Árabes Unidos" }, 
{"question": "🇦🇹", "response": "Austria" }, 
{"question": "🇧🇭", "response": "Baréin" }, 
{"question": "🇧🇬", "response": "Bulgaria" }, 
{"question": "🇨🇮", "response": "Costa de Marfil" }, 
{"question": "🇨🇳", "response": "China" }, 
{"question": "🇯🇵", "response": "Japón" }, 
{"question": "🇩🇪", "response": "Alemania" },
{"question": "🇱🇻", "response": "Letonia" }, 
{"question": "🇵🇷", "response": "Puerto Rico" }, 
{"question": "🇧🇷", "response": "Brasil" }, 
{"question": "🇧🇫", "response": "Burkina Faso" }, 
{"question": "🇵🇦", "response": "Panamá" }, 
{"question": "🇹🇯", "response": "Tayikistán" }, 
{"question": "🇬🇷", "response": "Grecia" }, 
{"question": "🇹🇬", "response": "Togo" }, 
{"question": "🇲🇲", "response": "Birmania" }, 
{"question": "🇲🇦", "response": "Marruecos" }, 
{"question": "🇳🇪", "response": "Níger" }, 
{"question": "🇵🇾", "response": "Paraguay" }
]